Guide to the Foundation for Southeast Asian Art and Culture records, 1954-2002 and undated
Duke University. University Archives
- Administrative Records, 1960-2002 and undated
  - General Ledger, 1978-1998 (Folder 2 of 3) (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - General Ledger. 1970–1977 (Oversize-box 13, Box 12)
  - General Ledger, 1978-1998 (Folder 3 of 3) (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - N.Y. Office Vouchers, No. 1, July 1961–August 1965 (1 of 4) (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - N.Y. Office Vouchers, No. 1, July 1961–August 1965 (2 of 4) (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - N.Y. Office Vouchers, No. 1, July 1961–August 1965 (3 of 4) (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - N.Y. Office Vouchers, No. 1, July 1961–August 1965 (4 of 4) (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - N.Y. Office Vouchers, No. 2, September 1965–June 30, 1972 (1 of 5) (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - N.Y. Office Vouchers, No. 2, September 1965–June 30, 1972 (2 of 5) (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - N.Y. Office Vouchers, No. 2, September 1965–June 30, 1972 (3 of 5) (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - N.Y. Office Vouchers, No. 2, September 1965–June 30, 1972 (4 of 5) (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - N.Y. Office Vouchers, No. 2, September 1965–June 30, 1972 (5 of 5) (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - N.Y. Office Vouchers, No. 3, Vouchers No. 583–749, July 1972–December 31, 1972 (1 of 6) (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - N.Y. Office Vouchers, No. 3, Vouchers No. 583–749, July 1972–December 31, 1972 (2 of 6) (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - N.Y. Office Vouchers, No. 3, Vouchers No. 583–749, July 1972–December 31, 1972 (3 of 6) (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - N.Y. Office Vouchers, No. 3, Vouchers No. 583–749, July 1972–December 31, 1972 (4 of 6) (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - N.Y. Office Vouchers, No. 3, Vouchers No. 583–749, July 1972–December 31, 1972 (5 of 6) (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - N.Y. Office Vouchers, No. 3, Vouchers No. 583–749, July 1972–December 31, 1972 (6 of 6) (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - N.Y. Office Vouchers, No. 4, Vouchers No. 750–895, January 1, 1973–October 31, 1973 (1 of 5) (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - N.Y. Office Vouchers, No. 4, Vouchers No. 750–895, January 1, 1973–October 31, 1973 (2 of 5) (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - N.Y. Office Vouchers, No. 4, Vouchers No. 750–895, January 1, 1973–October 31, 1973 (3 of 5) (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - N.Y. Office Vouchers, No. 4, Vouchers No. 750–895, January 1, 1973–October 31, 1973 (4 of 5) (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - N.Y. Office Vouchers, No. 4, Vouchers No. 750–895, January 1, 1973–October 31, 1973 (5 of 5) (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - N.Y. Office Vouchers, No. 5, Vouchers No. 896–1077, November 1, 1973–October 31, 1975 (1 of 5) (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - N.Y. Office Vouchers, No. 5, Vouchers No. 896–1077, November 1, 1973–October 31, 1975 (2 of 5) (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - N.Y. Office Vouchers, No. 5, Vouchers No. 896–1077, November 1, 1973–October 31, 1975 (3 of 5) (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - N.Y. Office Vouchers, No. 5, Vouchers No. 896–1077, November 1, 1973–October 31, 1975 (4 of 5) (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - N.Y. Office Vouchers, No. 5, Vouchers No. 896–1077, November 1, 1973–October 31, 1975 (5 of 5) (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - N.Y. Office Vouchers, No. 6, Vouchers No. 1078–1313, November 1, 1975–December 31, 1978 (1 of 6) (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - N.Y. Office Vouchers, No. 6, Vouchers No. 1078–1313, November 1, 1975–December 31, 1978 (2 of 6) (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - N.Y. Office Vouchers, No. 6, Vouchers No. 1078–1313, November 1, 1975–December 31, 1978 (3 of 6) (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - N.Y. Office Vouchers, No. 6, Vouchers No. 1078–1313, November 1, 1975–December 31, 1978 (4 of 6) (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - N.Y. Office Vouchers, No. 6, Vouchers No. 1078–1313, November 1, 1975–December 31, 1978 (5 of 6) (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - N.Y. Office Vouchers, No. 6, Vouchers No. 1078–1313, November 1, 1975–December 31, 1978 (6 of 6) (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - N.Y. Office Vouchers, No. 7, Vouchers No. 1314–1540, M.G.T. Co. Account, January 1, 1979–August 15, 1986 (1 of 4) (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - N.Y. Office Vouchers, No. 7, Vouchers No. 1314–1540, M.G.T. Co. Account, January 1, 1979–August 15, 1986 (2 of 4) (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - N.Y. Office Vouchers, No. 7, Vouchers No. 1314–1540, M.G.T. Co. Account, January 1, 1979–August 15, 1986 (3 of 4) (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - N.Y. Office Vouchers, No. 7, Vouchers No. 1314–1540, M.G.T. Co. Account, January 1, 1979–August 15, 1986 (4 of 4) (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - N.Y. Office Vouchers, No. 7, Vouchers No. 1314–1540, M.G.T. Co. Account, January 1, 1979–August 15, 1986 (1 of 2) (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - N.Y. Office Vouchers, No. 7, Vouchers No. 1314–1540, M.G.T. Co. Account, January 1, 1979–August 15, 1986 (2 of 2) (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Accountings of bond and special journal entries, No. 1, December 1963–December 1968 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Honolulu Summary Statements, No. 1, April 1963–December 1966 (1 of 5) (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Honolulu Summary Statements, No. 1, April 1963–December 1966 (2 of 5) (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Honolulu Summary Statements, No. 1, April 1963–December 1966 (3 of 5) (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Honolulu Summary Statements, No. 1, April 1963–December 1966 (4 of 5) (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Honolulu Summary Statements, No. 1, April 1963–December 1966 (5 of 5) (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Honolulu Summary Statements, No. 2, January 1967–December 1971 (1 of 5) (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Honolulu Summary Statements, No. 2, January 1967–December 1971 (2 of 5) (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Honolulu Summary Statements, No. 2, January 1967–December 1971 (3 of 5) (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Honolulu Summary Statements, No. 2, January 1967–December 1971 (4 of 5) (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Honolulu Summary Statements, No. 2, January 1967–December 1971 (5 of 5) (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Honolulu Summary Statements, No. 3, January 1972–August 1972 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - SEAAC Reeservations, 1974-1978 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Fact Sheet, circa 1972 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Tour Reservation Schedules, 1972-1973 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - SEAAC Control Sheets, Deposits and Withdrawal Transfers, 1972-1973 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Newspaper Reporters, 1972-1973 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - SEAAC Ticket Control, 1972-1973 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - SEAAC, Penson Company, Violet Mimaki, Copies Number 2, 1972 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - SEAAC, Penson Company, Copies, Weissburger, 1972-1973 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - William Eaton, Copies (Incomplete) Number 2, 1972 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - SEAAC, Carter, Ledyard and Millburn, Copies, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - SEAAC General Administrative Documents, 1974-1981 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - SEAAC General Administrative Documents, 1962-1968 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - SEAAC Vehicle, 1970 Volkswagon, 1974 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - SEAAC Progress Reports, 1973-1974 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - SEAAC Information, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - SEAAC Electrical Supplies, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - SEAAC Fumigation, 1972 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - SEAAC Garbage Disposal, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - SEAAC Insurance, 1972-1973 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - SEAAC Office Inventory, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - SEAAC Thai Village, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - SEAAC Correspondence with Drs. Tashijan and Kittleson, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - SEAAC Local Correspondence and Estimates, 1972-1973 (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - SEAAC Exhibit, Letters of Thanks and Compliments, 1973-1978 (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - SEAAC Correspondence, Mrs. Violet Mimaki, 1972-1973 (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - SEAAC, Julius Lowy Estimates, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - SEAAC Requisitions, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - SEAAC Requisitions, 1974 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - SEAAC Paid Bills, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - SEAAC Paid Bills, 1972 (2 folders) (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - SEAAC Personnel, 1973-1974 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Howard Unich, 1973-1974 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Raymond Milhime, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Hugh Curtis, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - New Jersey Tax Exemption Board, 1972, undated (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Elisbeth McConville, 1973-1974 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - SEAAC Art Restoration, 1972-1973 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - SEAAC Painting Supplies, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - SEAAC Antique Dealer, Paris, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - SEAAC Fire Alarm, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - SEAAC Security Control, 1972-1973 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - SEAAC Burgler Alarm, 1972-1974 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - SEAAC, Park Travel Agency, 1972-1973 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - SEAAC, U.S. Line, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Trailvan Service, undated (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - SEAAC Damaged Shipment, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Mr. Amar's Personal Items Paid for by Mr. Amar, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - SEAAC Bills, 1974 (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - SEAAC Requisitions, 1973-1974, undated (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - SEAAC Images of Objects, undated (2 folders) (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - "The Lacquer Pavilion at Suan Pakkad Palace", book, undated (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Tennis Court Priests Chair, undated (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Duplicates, including images, undated (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Liz McConville, General Administrative Documents, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - SEAAC Photographs Reference (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Check Stubs, Morgan Trust Co. Account Number 165-11-477, 1977-1984 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Original Bills, Numbers 511-577, 1962-1963 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Original Bills, Numbers 578-629 and unnumbered, 1963-1964 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Purchase Book, 1960-1963 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Bills, Numbers 300-399, 1961-1962 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Purchase Book, Bills, Numbers 386-510, 1962 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Purchase Book, Bills, Numbers 1-385, 1960-1962 (3 folders) (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Photographs of Various Tiles Taken by Howard wong, AIA of the Royal Dusit Palace Grounds, undated (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - 16 8x10 inch Color Prints of Tiles for Temple and Pantheon, undated (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Letter to Doris Duke from Violet Mimaki Regarding Drawings of the Thai Houses, 1971 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Loose Photographs and Negatives, undated (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Copies of Purchase Book Bills, Numbers 1-99, 1960-1961 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Letter Regarding Ticket Payments, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Copies of Purchase Book Bills, Numbers 500-625 and Unnumbered, Photograph of Lamp, 1962-1963, undated (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Copies of Bills, Numbers 400-499, 1962 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Copies of Bills, Numbers 100-199, 1961 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Copies of Bills, Numbers 200-299, 1961 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Financial Records, Chemical Bank, 1986-1989 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Ticket Control and Reserved Ticket Information, 1973-1983 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence to Elizabeth McConville, 1978-1979, undated (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Thailand Postcards and Brochures, 1972-1973 (folder 1 of 2) (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Thailand Postcards and Brochures, 1972-1973 (folder 2 of 2) (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - SEAAC Tax Returns Letter, 1982 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - SEAAC Letterhead and Purchase Order Forms, undated (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - SEAAC Reservations Book, 1972-1974 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Photographs of Thai Villiage Model and Land Surveys, circa 1963 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Drawings of Thai Palace, Photographs of Objects and Doris Duke Possibly on Her Honeymoon, circa 1930s-1960s (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - SEAAC Inventory, Tennis Court Closet Number 1, undated (folder 1 of 3) (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - SEAAC Inventory, Tennis Court Closet Number 1, undated (folders 2 and 3 of 3) (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - SEAAC Inventory, Unknown Location, undated (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - SEAAC Inventory, Tennis Court Closet Number 2, undated (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - SEAAC Inventory, Coach Barn Exhibit Book Number 2, undated (1 of 3) (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - SEAAC Inventory, Coach Barn Exhibit Book Number 2, undated (2 of 3) (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - SEAAC Inventory, Coach Barn Exhibit Book Number 2, undated (3 of 3) (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, Reservation Cancellations and Notes Regarding Object Locations, 1977-1982, undated (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - SEAAC Financial Statements, 1988 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Pete E. Cooley Folder of Correspondence, Documents Regarding Francois Duchau and Financial Records, 1960-1963 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - SEAAC Trial Balances, 1961-1965 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Haiku Brochure prepared for Bishop Estate Presentation, Architect's copy (unbound) from Wong & Wong, architects, circa 1960s (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - General correspondence and other documents related to SEAAC administration, 1964-1965 and undated (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Lou Pursel's Sketches of Thai Houses. Louis Pursel, architect. Undated. Color pencil and pencil on diazo. (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Notes for SEAAC, 1985 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Wrong Pavilion Drawings, 1964 (2 folders) (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Photographs of Houses in Bangkok, undated (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Photographs from Somchai Roomsamuk, undated (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Ledger, 1961-1964 (Oversize-box 33, Box 32)
  - Ledger: Cashbook February 1961-December 1964, Journal January 1961-January 1965 (Oversize-box 33, Box 32)
  - Foundation for Southeast Asian Art & Culture - Model for Thai Village Complex, circa 1963 (Box 39)
  - Preliminary Report on Thai Village Site Green Valley, Punaluu, 1963 Aug 27 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - SEAAC Journal, 1969-1977, SEAAC Cashbook, 1965-1969 (1 of 3) (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - SEAAC Journal, 1969-1977, SEAAC Cashbook, 1965-1969 (2 of 3) (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - SEAAC Journal, 1969-1977, SEAAC Cashbook, 1965-1969 (3 of 3) (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - SEAAC-Art Objects invoices, 1965 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Foundation for Southeast Asian Art and Culture inventory of art objects, 1971 Jan 8 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - SEACC-Coach Barn Exhibit Book #3, inventory #1000-1500, circa 1972 (1 of 4) (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - SEACC-Coach Barn Exhibit Book #3, inventory #1000-1500, circa 1972 (2 of 4) (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - SEACC-Coach Barn Exhibit Book #3, inventory #1000-1500, circa 1972 (3 of 4) (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - SEACC-Coach Barn Exhibit Book #3, inventory #1000-1500, circa 1972 (4 of 4) (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - SEAAC-Coach Barn Exhibit, Inventory #1-400, circa 1970s (1 of 4) (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - SEAAC-Coach Barn Exhibit, Inventory #1-400, circa 1970s (2 of 4) (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - SEAAC-Coach Barn Exhibit, Inventory #1-400, circa 1970s (3 of 4) (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - SEAAC-Coach Barn Exhibit, Inventory #1-400, circa 1970s (4 of 4) (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - SEAAC Inventory, circa 1970s (1 of 5) (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - SEAAC Inventory, circa 1970s (2 of 5) (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - SEAAC Inventory, circa 1970s (3 of 5) (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - SEAAC Inventory, circa 1970s (4 of 5) (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - SEAAC Inventory, circa 1970s (5of 5) (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - SEAAC Inventory, items 1-200, circa 1970s (1 of 6) (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - SEAAC Inventory, items 1-200, circa 1970s (2 of 6) (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - SEAAC Inventory, items 1-200, circa 1970s (3 of 6) (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - SEAAC Inventory, items 1-200, circa 1970s (4 of 6) (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - SEAAC Inventory, items 1-200, circa 1970s (5 of 6) (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - SEAAC Inventory, items 1-200, circa 1970s (6 of 6) (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - SEAAC Inventory, items 201-400, circa 1970s (1 of 5) (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - SEAAC Inventory, items 201-400, circa 1970s (2 of 5) (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - SEAAC Inventory, items 201-400, circa 1970s (3 of 5) (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - SEAAC Inventory, items 201-400, circa 1970s (4 of 5) (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - SEAAC Inventory, items 201-400, circa 1970s (5 of 5) (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - SEAAC Inventory, items 401-600, circa 1970s (1 of 6) (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - SEAAC Inventory, items 401-600, circa 1970s (2 of 6) (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - SEAAC Inventory, items 401-600, circa 1970s (3 of 6) (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - SEAAC Inventory, items 401-600, circa 1970s (4 of 6) (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - SEAAC Inventory, items 401-600, circa 1970s (5 of 6) (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - SEAAC Inventory, items 401-600, circa 1970s (6 of 6) (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - SEAAC Inventory, items 601-800, circa 1970s (1 of 6) (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - SEAAC Inventory, items 601-800, circa 1970s (2 of 6) (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - SEAAC Inventory, items 601-800, circa 1970s (3 of 6) (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - SEAAC Inventory, items 601-800, circa 1970s (4 of 6) (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - SEAAC Inventory, items 601-800, circa 1970s (5 of 6) (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - SEAAC Inventory, items 601-800, circa 1970s (6 of 6) (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - SEAAC Inventory, items 1-67c., circa 1970s (1 of 5) (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - SEAAC Inventory, items 1-67c., circa 1970s (2 of 5) (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - SEAAC Inventory, items 1-67c., circa 1970s (3 of 5) (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - SEAAC Inventory, items 1-67c., circa 1970s (4 of 5) (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - SEAAC Inventory, items 1-67c., circa 1970s (5 of 5) (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - SEAAC Inventory, items 67d-199.2, circa 1970s (1 of 4) (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - SEAAC Inventory, items 67d-199.2, circa 1970s (2 of 4) (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - SEAAC Inventory, items 67d-199.2, circa 1970s (3 of 4) (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - SEAAC Inventory, items 67d-199.2, circa 1970s (4 of 4) (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - SEAAC Inventory, items 207.A-289, circa 1970s (1 of 3) (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - SEAAC Inventory, items 207.A-289, circa 1970s (2 of 3) (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - SEAAC Inventory, items 207.A-289, circa 1970s (3 of 3) (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - SEAAC Inventory, items 290.1A-435, circa 1970s (1 of 3) (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - SEAAC Inventory, items 290.1A-435, circa 1970s (2 of 3) (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - SEAAC Inventory, items 290.1A-435, circa 1970s (3 of 3) (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - SEAAC Inventory, items 439-576, circa 1970s (1 of 2) (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - SEAAC Inventory, items 439-576, circa 1970s (2 of 2) (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - SEAAC Inventory-Vol II, items 436-574.1, circa 1970s (1 of 3) (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - SEAAC Inventory-Vol II, items 436-574.1, circa 1970s (2 of 3) (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - SEAAC Inventory-Vol II, items 436-574.1, circa 1970s (3 of 3) (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - SEAAC Inventory-Vol II, items 574.2-647, circa 1970s (1 of 2) (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - SEAAC Inventory-Vol II, items 574.2-647, circa 1970s (2 of 2) (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - SEAAC Inventory-Miscellaneous, circa 1970s (1 of 3) (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - SEAAC Inventory-Miscellaneous, circa 1970s (2 of 3) (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - SEAAC Inventory-Miscellaneous, circa 1970s (3 of 3) (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - SEAAC Inventory-Photocopies, circa 1970s (1 of 2) (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - SEAAC Inventory-Photocopies, circa 1970s (2 of 2) (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - SEAAC Shooting Gallery Inventory, circa 1970s (1 of 4) (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - SEAAC Shooting Gallery Inventory, circa 1970s (2 of 4) (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - SEAAC Shooting Gallery Inventory, circa 1970s (3 of 4) (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - SEAAC Shooting Gallery Inventory, circa 1970s (4 of 4) (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Thai House Foundation Board Book. Includes Certificate of Incorporation, 1961-1963 (Box 52)
  - Foundation for Southeast Asian Art and Culture Board Book, 1964-1973 (Box 52)
  - Insurance for art objects, automobile and Pavilion as part of the Foundation for Southeast Asian Art and Culture, 1963-1972 (1 of 2) (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Insurance for art objects, automobile and Pavilion as part of the Foundation for Southeast Asian Art and Culture, 1963-1972 (2 of 2) (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Memoranda and correspondence related to items for purchase for SEAAC, including books and wood carvings. Includes black and white photographs, 1965-1967 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence and other documents regarding the sale of the Haiku Land in Hawaii by the Foundation for Southeast Asian Art and Culture, 1969-1972 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Bill of lading for shipment of village parts from Hawaii to Duke Farms, 1972 (Box 53, Folder 5)
- Photographs, circa 1960-1969 (Box 53)
  The black and white photographs in this series primarily document the art objects and building parts purchased by Doris Duke for SEAAC. Each object and building part was photographed and many include a short hand written description of what it is. Sculpture comprises the largest group of holdings in this collection, with a majority of them serving a religious purpose, but also documented are manuscript cabinets, manuscripts, paintings, chests, jars, Thai fabrics, ceramics, teapots, swords, masks, boxes, and musical instruments. Also included on a much smaller scale, are color photographs of the actual buildings that were to be duplicated in the Thai Village. The photographs are arranged alphabetically and numerically thereunder.
  - SEAAC Inventory - color images, undated (1 of 2) (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - SEAAC Inventory - color images, undated (2 of 2) (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - SEAAC Inventory - color images of Travelling Jewelry Case, undated (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - SEAAC Inventory - items located in Residence (color images), undated (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - SEAAC Inventory - items that could not be located in SEAAC and Shooting Gallery (photocopies of images), undated (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - SEAAC Inventory - photocopies of Jewelry, undated (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Black and White Photo, Small Sala in Emerld Buddha, Temple Compound, undated (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Black and White Photos, Wall of Royal Palace, undated (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Color Photos, Burma Wall, undated (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Color Photos, Chapel Royal, 1964 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Color Photos, Royal Patheon, 1964 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Color Photos, Temple Detail, 1964 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Baskets, Boxes (1 of 2) (Box 35)
  - Baskets, Boxes (2 of 2) (Box 35)
  - Bowls, Plates, Spoons, Teapots, Jugs, (1 of 11) (Box 35)
  - Bowls, Plates, Spoons, Teapots, Jugs, (2 of 11) (Box 35)
  - Bowls, Plates, Spoons, Teapots, Jugs, (3 of 11) (Box 35)
  - Bowls, Plates, Spoons, Teapots, Jugs, (4 of 11) (Box 35)
  - Bowls, Plates, Spoons, Teapots, Jugs, (5 of 11) (Box 35)
  - Bowls, Plates, Spoons, Teapots, Jugs, (6 of 11) (Box 35)
  - Bowls, Plates, Spoons, Teapots, Jugs, (7 of 11) (Box 35)
  - Bowls, Plates, Spoons, Teapots, Jugs, (8 of 11) (Box 35)
  - Bowls, Plates, Spoons, Teapots, Jugs, (9 of 11) (Box 35)
  - Bowls, Plates, Spoons, Teapots, Jugs, (10 of 11) (Box 35)
  - Bowls, Plates, Spoons, Teapots, Jugs, (11 of 11) (Box 35)
  - Building Parts, 1, 2 (Box 35)
  - Building Parts, 1A, 1B, 1C, 1D (Box 35)
  - Building Parts, 2-4 (Box 35)
  - Building Parts, 4,5 (Box 35)
  - Building Parts, 1, 2 (Box 35)
  - Building Parts, 6, 10-14 (Box 35)
  - Building Parts, 15-19 (Box 35)
  - Building Parts, 20-25 (Box 35)
  - Building Parts, 26-31 (Box 35)
  - Building Parts, 32-37 (Box 35)
  - Building Parts, 38-41 (Box 35)
  - Building Parts, 42-45 (Box 35)
  - Building Parts, 45, 46, 48-50 (Box 35)
  - Building Parts, 52 (Box 35)
  - Building Parts, 53-56 (Box 35)
  - Building Parts, 57-60 (Box 35)
  - Building Parts, 61-63 (Box 35)
  - Building Parts, 64-68 (Box 35)
  - Building Parts, 69-71 (Box 35)
  - Building Parts, 72-74 (Box 35)
  - Building Parts, 72,73 (Box 35)
  - Building Parts, 74-77 (Box 35)
  - Building Parts, 78-82 (Box 35)
  - Building Parts, 85-89 (Box 35)
  - Building Parts, 90-95 (Box 35)
  - Building Parts, 96-99 (Box 35)
  - Building Parts, 100-102 (Box 35)
  - Building Parts, 103-105 (Box 35)
  - Building Parts, 106-111 (Box 35)
  - Building Parts, 112-114 (Box 35)
  - Building Parts, 115-118 (Box 35)
  - Building Parts, 119-122 (Box 35)
  - Building Parts, 123, 127-130 (Box 35)
  - Building Parts, 124-126 (Box 35)
  - Building Parts, 131-136 (Box 35)
  - Building Parts, 137-142 (Box 35)
  - Building Parts, 143-147 (Box 35)
  - Building Parts, 149-154 (Box 35)
  - Building Parts, 155-160 (Box 35)
  - Building Parts, 161, 162, 164-166 (Box 35)
  - Building Parts, 163, 167-170 (Box 36)
  - Building Parts, 171-175 (Box 36)
  - Building Parts, 176-181 (Box 36)
  - Building Parts, 182-187 (Box 36)
  - Building Parts, 188-193 (Box 36)
  - Building Parts, 194-198 (Box 36)
  - Building Parts, 200, 202-204 (Box 36)
  - Building Parts, 201, 206, 207, 209, 210 (Box 36)
  - Building Parts, 208, 220, 229 (Box 36)
  - Building Parts, 211-216 (Box 36)
  - Building Parts, 217-219, 221, 222 (Box 36)